Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #4 (Order Department)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders, alphabetical by customer name (37 volumes, many duplicate, usually annual, housed in 14 folders) Small order log books,1980-1981 (Box 91, Folder 1693)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – Secretaries' order books,1949-1950, 1952-1953 (Box 92, Folder 1694)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – Order numbers,1951-1981 (Box 92, Folder 1695)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – Secretaries' order books,1953-1954, 1956-1958 (Box 92, Folder 1696)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – looseleaf order binders, #58001-64147,1958-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1697)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – looseleaf order binders, #65001-71169,1965-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1698)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – looseleaf order binders, #72001-81014,1972-1981 (Box 92, Folder 1699)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books – looseleaf order binders,1976-1981 (Box 92, Folder 1700)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order index,1967-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1701)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order log books,1961-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1702)
  - Records, Orders - Indexes to Orders: 1961-1967, 1970-1980 alphabetical by customer name (10 volumes, duplicating information in preceding volumes, housed in 4 folders); 1949-1957, alphabetical by model name (9 volumes housed in 2 volumes); 1951-1957, organized by order number (4 volumes); 1958-1981, organized by order number (#58001-81014) and includes address where house built (3 folders) - Small order book,1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 1703)
  - Records, Orders - Customer order forms - 1914-1915, book, order numbers 3789-4575,1914-1915 (Box 93, Folder 1704)
  - Records, Orders - Customer order forms - sample form with instructions for processing,1977-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1705)
  - Records, Orders - Customer order forms - sample form with instructions for processing,1977-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1706)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4576-4602,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1707)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4603-4632,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1708)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4633-4653,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1709)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4654-4678,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1710)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4679-4702,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1711)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4703-4735,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1712)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4736-4764,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1713)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4765-4799,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1714)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4800-4830,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1715)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4831-4860,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1716)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4861-4890,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1717)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4891-4920,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1718)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4921-4950,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1719)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4951-4980,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1720)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #4981-5009,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1721)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5010-5040,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1722)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5041-5070,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1723)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5071-5100,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1724)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5101-5145,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1725)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5146-5175,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1726)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5176-5205,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1727)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5206-5234,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1728)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5235-5264,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1729)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5265-5294,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1730)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #5295-5328,1915 (Box 94, Folder 1731)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 5328-6075,1916 (Box 95, Folder 1732)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 6076-6900,1916 (Box 96, Folder 1733)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 6901-7888,1916 (Box 97, Folder 1734)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 7889-9000,1917 (Box 98, Folder 1735)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 9001-10099,1917 (Box 99, Folder 1736)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 10100-11167,1917 (Box 100, Folder 1737)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 11200-12159 (some gaps),1918 (Box 101, Folder 1738)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12160-12203 ½ (1918),1918 (Box 102, Folder 1739)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12204-12277 ½,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1740)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12278-12307,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1741)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12308-12351,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1742)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12352-12407,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1743)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12408-12444,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1744)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12445-12480,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1745)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12481-12508,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1746)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12509-12544,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1747)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12545-12601,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1748)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12602-12633,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1749)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12634-12669 ½,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1750)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12670-12702,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1751)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12703-12733,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1752)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12734-12779,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1753)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12780-12809,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1754)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12810-12846,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1755)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #12847-13029,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1756)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13030-13062,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1757)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13063-13109,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1758)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13110-13410,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1759)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13411-13441,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1760)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13442-13496,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1761)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #13496 ½-14000,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1762)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14001-14034,1918 (Box 102, Folder 1763)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14035½-14065,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1764)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14066-14096,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1765)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14097-14127,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1766)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14128-14158,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1767)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14159-14189,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1768)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14190-14220,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1769)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14221-14251,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1770)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14252-14282,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1771)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14284-14314 ½,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1772)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14315-14345,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1773)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14346-14376,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1774)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14377-14407,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1775)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14408-14438½,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1776)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14439-14469,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1777)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14470-14528,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1778)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14529-14559,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1779)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14560-14590,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1780)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14591-14621,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1781)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14621½-14651,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1782)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14652-14682,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1783)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14683-14713,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1784)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14714-14744,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1785)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14745-14775,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1786)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14776-14806,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1787)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #S-14807-14837,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1788)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14838-14868,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1789)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14869-14899,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1790)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14900-14930,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1791)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14931-14961, some photocopies,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1792)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #14961½-14976, photocopies,1919 (Box 103, Folder 1793)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 14976-16034,1919 (Box 104, Folder 1794)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 16035-17015,1919 (Box 105, Folder 1795)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 17016-17949,1920 (Box 106, Folder 1796)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #17960-17989,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1797)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #17990-18524,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1798)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18525-18560,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1799)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18561-18599,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1800)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18600-18636,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1801)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18637-18677,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1802)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18678-18710,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1803)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18711-18741,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1804)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18742-18774,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1805)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18775-18800,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1806)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18801-18840,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1807)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18841-18870,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1808)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18871-18900,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1809)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18901-18952,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1810)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18953-18975,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1811)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #18976-18999,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1812)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19000-19051,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1813)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19052-19074,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1814)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19075-19136,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1815)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19136-19176,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1816)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19177-19203,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1817)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19204-19236,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1818)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19237-19298,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1819)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19299-19344,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1820)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #19345-19387,1920 (Box 107, Folder 1821)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 21000-21482,1921 (Box 108, Folder 1822)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 21483-22091,1921 (Box 109, Folder 1823)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - 1922, book, order numbers 22092-22586,1922 (Box 110, Folder 1824)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 22587-23180,1922 (Box 111, Folder 1825)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #24401.08-23230,1922-1923 (Box 112, Folder 1826)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23231-23260,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1827)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23261-23290,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1828)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23291-23321,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1829)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23322-23352,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1830)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23353-23383,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1831)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23384-23414,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1832)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23415-23445,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1833)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23446-23476,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1834)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23477-23507,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1835)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23508-23538,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1836)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23539-23569,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1837)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23570-23600,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1838)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23632-23662,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1839)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23601-23631,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1840)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23663-23693,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1841)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23694-23725,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1842)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23726-23756,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1843)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23757-23787 ½,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1844)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23788-23878,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1845)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23819-23850 ½,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1846)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #23851-23923,1923 (Box 112, Folder 1847)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 23924-24454,1923 (Box 113, Folder 1848)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 24455-26212,1924 (Box 114, Folder 1849)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 26213-26860,1924 (Box 115, Folder 1850)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 26861-27684,1925 (Box 116, Folder 1851)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 27685-28655,1925 (Box 117, Folder 1852)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 28656-29536,1926 (Box 118, Folder 1853)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 29537-323131926 (Box 119, Folder 1854)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 32314-33703,1927 (Box 120, Folder 1855)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 33704-34862,1928 (Box 121, Folder 1856)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 34683-35438,1929 (Box 122, Folder 1857)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 35439-35858,1930 (Box 123, Folder 1858)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 35959-36673,1931-1932 (Box 124, Folder 1859)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36677-36700,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1860)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36700-36735,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1861)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36736-36770,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1862)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36771-36800,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1863)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36801-36835,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1864)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36836-36870,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1865)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36871-36900,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1866)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36901-36935,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1867)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36936-36970,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1868)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #36971-36999,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1869)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37000-37034,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1870)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37035-37070,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1871)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37071-37100,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1872)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37101-37135,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1873)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37136-37170,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1874)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37171-37200,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1875)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37201-37235,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1876)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37236-37270,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1877)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37271-37300,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1878)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37301-37335,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1879)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37336-37370,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1880)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37371-37399,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1881)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #37400-27447,1933-1936 (Box 125, Folder 1882)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - order numbers 37448-38099,1937-1939 (Box 126, Folder 1883)
  - Empty folder,undated (Box 127, Folder 1884)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38100-38130,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1885)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38131-38170,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1886)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38171-38200,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1887)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38201-38230,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1888)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38231-38270,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1889)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38271-38300,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1890)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38301-38330,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1891)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38331-38370,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1892)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38371-38400,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1893)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38401-38430,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1894)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38431-38470,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1895)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38471-38500,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1896)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38501-38530,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1897)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38531-38570,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1898)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38571-38605,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1899)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38606-38670,1940-1945 (Box 127, Folder 1900)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #38671-38798,1940-1948 (Box 127, Folder 1901)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Invoices – orders #23096-23137,1942-1944 (Box 127, Folder 1902)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 39001-39948,1947-1948 (Box 128, Folder 1903)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 4901-49912,1949 (Box 129, Folder 1904)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 50001-50600,1950 (Box 130, Folder 1905)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - order numbers 50601-51200 (book incorrectly labeled 50001-50600),1950 (Box 131, Folder 1906)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 51201-51811,1950 (Box 132, Folder 1907)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 52000-52543,1951 (Box 133, Folder 1908)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - book, order numbers 524444-53087,1951 (Box 134, Folder 1909)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53101-53131,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1910)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53132-33162,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1911)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53163-53193,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1912)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53194-53224,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1913)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53225-53256,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1914)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53257-53287,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1915)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53288-53318,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1916)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53319-53349,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1917)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53350-53380,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1918)
  - Records, Customer Order Forms - Orders #53381-53411,1952 (Box 135, Folder 1919)